Look at that.
Another new coffee shop.
- You see that?
- Totally. Yeah.
- What's that one called?
- Foam Party.
"Foam Party"? Come on.
And everyone is just linin' up.
You see that?
I see it.
Is that a coffee shop
or a disco?
Dad, you're old, man.
There are multiple reports
of another mysterious
seismic event last night.
Sources close to Spider-Man say
he's looking into the problem.
Spider-Man. I mean,
this guy swings in once a day,
zip-zap-zop in his little mask
and answers to no one. Right?
Yeah, Dad. Yeah.
Meanwhile,
my guys are out there,
- lives on the line, no masks.
- Uh-huh.
- We show our faces.
- Speed up. I know these kids.
With great ability
comes great accountability.
That's not even
how the saying goes.
I do like his cereal, though.
I'll give him that.
Oh, my gosh.
Don't cops run red lights?
Oh, yeah, some do.
But not your dad.
♪ My memories keep begging ♪
♪ For someone else ♪
♪ I know this feeling, yes
I know it very well ♪
Why can't I go back
to Brooklyn Middle?
You've given it
two weeks.
We're not having
this conversation.
I just think that
this new school is elitist.
- "Elitist"?
- And I would prefer to be
at a normal school
among the people.
"The people"?
These are your people.
I'm only here 'cause
I won that stupid lottery.
No way. You passed the entry
test just like everybody else.
You have an opportunity here.
You wanna blow that?
You wanna end up
like your uncle?
What's wrong with Uncle Aaron?
He's a good guy.
We all make choices in life.
It doesn't feel
like I have a choice right now.
You don't!
I love you, Miles.
Yeah, I know, Dad.
See you Friday.
- You gotta say "I love you" back.
- Dad, are you serious?
I wanna hear it.
"I love you, Dad."
You wanna hear me
say it?
You're dropping me off
at a school.
- "I love you, Dad."
- Look at this place.
"Dad, I love you."
Dad, I love you.
That's a copy.